[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not one of the defense mechanisms against viruses in humans?", "correct_answer": "The resistance (R) gene", "incorrect_answers": ["Acid nature of the stomach contents", "RNA interference", "Production of antibodies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What hairstyle combines the 1950s pompadour, the 50s flattop, and sometimes a mohawk?", "correct_answer": "Quiff", "incorrect_answers": ["Shag", "Induction cut", "High and tight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie directed by Oliver Stone to win the Academy Award for Best Picture?", "correct_answer": "Platoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Heaven  Earth", "Born on the Fourth of July", "JFK"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 2 Fast 2 Furious, what car did Brian OConner (Paul Walkers character) drive in the opening street race?", "correct_answer": "Nissan Skyline", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitsubishi Lancer Evo VII", "Mitsubishi Eclipse Spyder", "Toyota Supra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Treatment of asthma with a long-acting beta agonist is inadvisable unless you are also treating the asthma with a steroid.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is an ordinal number?", "correct_answer": "A number that shows order", "incorrect_answers": ["A number involving i", "A number that shows the number of elements in a set", "A number that is less than zero"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Early in the movie The Pursuit of Happyness a woman steals something important from Chris. Who portrays this woman?", "correct_answer": "Joyful Raven", "incorrect_answers": ["Gabriel Union", "Florence Mitchell", "Martina Grayhurst"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Number One American movie song of all time as voted by the AFI is...", "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["Its Hard Out Here for a Pimp", "White Christmas", "Climb Every Mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1973 movie won the Oscar for Best Picture at the 46th Academy Awards ceremony in 1974?", "correct_answer": "The Sting", "incorrect_answers": ["Cries and Whispers", "The Exorcist", "A Touch of Class"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does KIT mean in instant messaging language?", "correct_answer": "keep in touch", "incorrect_answers": ["kiss it tenderly", "kook in training", "kitchen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the 1980 movie from this quote: Hey, professor! I recognize these teeth. This is Felipe Ocanya. He knew the jungle as well as I do.", "correct_answer": "Cannibal Holocaust", "incorrect_answers": ["Predator", "Motel Hell", "Bad Taste"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did French engineer Louis Reard invent in 1946 ?", "correct_answer": "the Bikini", "incorrect_answers": ["the first complete fossil of a triceratops", "the oversized catchers mitt", "the chemical test for prostate cancer (The PSA test)"]}]